Guide to the Time Inc. Fortune Publishing and Business Records 1929-2005 MS 3009-RG 25
New-York Historical Society
- Series V. Audiovisual [RESTRICTED], 1978-2005; 32 Linear feet in 32 record cartons
  - Subseries V.A. Fortune Editors on TV, 1992-2001; 15.25 Linear feet in 16 record cartons
    - Rob Norton: Prime News Saturday: CNN, 1993 August 7 (Offsite-box 2913, Item 17)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (22 min.): On label on case front: "Rob Norton Prime News Saturday CNN (Cable) August 7, 1993 8:00PM 22:00 Mins". On label on case side: "CNN/Rob Norton/8/7/93 Impact of Budget August 7, 1993 Fortune". On label on cassette: "Ken Norton/ Fortune Magazine August 7, 1993".
    - Sean Tully: This Morning's Business, 1993 August 13 (Offsite-box 2914, Item 1)
      1 videocassette (VHS) (3 min., 26 sec.): 1/2 in. On label on cassette front: "8/13 This Morning's Busi. S. Tully "Vatican's Finances" Start: 25:09; Ends: 28:35". On label on cassette side: "Sean Tully "This Morning's Busi." Fortune 8-13-93- Vatican's Finances (Starts 25:09; Ends 28:35)".
    - Moneytalk, 1993 September 1 (Offsite-box 2914, Item 2)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On cassette label: "Moneytalk 9/1/93-Fortune". Includes a sticker on cassette: "Dub".
    - Bill Saporito: Men's Fashion: NY1, 1993 September 3 (Offsite-box 2914, Item 3)
      1 videocassette (VHS): On label on case front: "Bill Saporito - NY1 - Men's Fashion 9/3/93". On label on case side: "Saporito 9/3/93 NY1-Men's Fashion".
    - Fortune Business Report, 1993 September 7 (Offsite-box 2914, Item 4)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case front and cassette: "Fortune Business Report segments from week of September 7, 1993". On label on case side: "9/7/93 Fortune Business Report September 1993".
    - Peter Nulty: Declining Gasoline Prices: Channel Two News at Five: WCBS-TV (CBS) New York, 1993 September 14 (Offsite-box 2914, Item 5)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (2 min., 24 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Peter Nulty, Declining Gasoline Prices' Channel Two News at Five WCBS-TV (CBS) New York September 14, 1993 5:00-6:00 PM 2:24". On label on case side: "Peter Nulty-Declining Gas Prices WCBS, TV 9/14/93 2:24".
    - Walter Kiechel: Boomers vs Busters: NY1 News, 1993 September 16 (Offsite-box 2914, Item 6)
      1 videocassette (VHS): On cassette label: "-Original- Fortune Walter Kiechel - 9-16-93 - NY1 News Boomers vs Busters".
    - Walter Kiechel: Busters vs. Boomers: NY1, 1993 September 17 (Offsite-box 2914, Item 7)
      1 videocassette (VHS): On cassette label: "Fortune Walter Kiechel on NY1 9-17-93 Busters vs. Boomers".
    - Geoff Colvin: Fortune Business Report: NY1 News, 1993 September 27 - October 1 (Offsite-box 2914, Item 8)
      1 videocassette (VHS): On label on cassette front: "Fortune Business Report Pull Reel for Geoff Colvin Sept.27 - Oct.1". On label on cassette side: "Geoff Colvin on NY1 News-- Fortune Business Report 9/27/93 -- 10/1/93".
    - Shawn Tully: Health Care Package: CNN, 1993 September 28 (Offsite-box 2914, Item 9)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On cassette label: "CNN-Shawn Tully 9-28-93 Health Care Package -Original-"
    - Shawn Tully: Healthcare Package: CNN, 1993 September 28 (Offsite-box 2914, Item 10)
      1 videocassette (VHS): On label on case front: "Shawn Tully on CNN Healthcare Package 9/28". On label on case side: "Shawn Tully 9-28-93 CNN-Healthcare Package Fortune".
    - Nancy Perry: Fear of Flying: NY1 News, 1993 September 30 (Offsite-box 2914, Item 11)
      1 videocassette (VHS): On cassette label: "Nancy Perry - NY1 News - 9-30-93 Fear of Flying
    - TV is the Thing: Fortune on Television, 1993 November (Offsite-box 2914, Item 12)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): On labels on case front and cassette: "'TV is the Thing' Fortune on Television". On label on case side: "1993 "TV is the Thing" Fortune on Television 11/93".
    - TV is the Thing: Fortune on Television, 1993 November (Offsite-box 2914, Item 13)
      1 videocassette (VHS): On label on case front: "'TV is the Thing' Fortune on Television 11/93". On label on case side: "1993 "TV is the Thing" Fortune on Television 11/93". On label on cassette: "'TV is the Thing' Fortune on Television".
    - Fortune Magazine: TV is the Thing, 1993 November (Offsite-box 2914, Item 14)
      1 videocassette (VHS): On labels on case and cassette: "Fortune Magazine "Tv is the Thing" 11/93".
    - John Curran, Fortune Magazine: NBC News Sunrise: NBC-TV, 1993 November 8 (Offsite-box 2914, Item 15)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (1 min., 54 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'John Curran, Fortune Magazine' NBC News Sunrise NBC-TV Network November 8, 1993 6:00-7:00 AM ET 1:54". On label on case side: "John Curran Fortune NBC News Sunrise 11-8-93".
    - Planning Magazine Covers: Dateline: NBC-TV, 1993 November 9 (Offsite-box 2914, Item 16)
      1 videocassette (VHS) (3 min., 51 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Planning Magazine Covers' Dateline NBC-TV Network November 9, 1993 10:00-11:00 PM ET 3:51". On label on case side: "Planning Magazine Covers Dateline, NBC, 11/9/93".
    - Ann Morrison: Christmas Shopping/Retailing: Good Morning America, 1993 November 26 (Offsite-box 2914, Item 17)
      1 videocassette (VHS): On cassette label: "Christmas Shopping/Retailing Good Morning America-Ann Morrison-11-26-93 (Outside Macy's) Fortune".
    - Geoffrey Colvin, Fortune Magazine: Good Day New York: WNYW-TV (Fox) New York, 1993 November 30 (Offsite-box 2914, Item 18)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (2 min., 44 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Geoffrey Colvin, Fortune Magazine' Good Day New York: 1st Edition WNYW-TV (Fox) New York November 30, 1993 6:00-7:00 AM 2:44". On label case side: "'Geoffrey Colvin, Fortune Magazine' Good Day New York: 1st Edition WNYW-TV (Fox) New York 11/30/93 6:00AM 2:44 Fortune".
    - Fortune Magazine/Hot New Products: Good Morning America: ABC-TV, 1993 December 8 (Offsite-box 2915, Item 1)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (45 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Fortune Magazine/Hot New Products' Good Morning America ABC-TV Network December 8, 1993 7:00-9:00 AM ET 0:45". On label on case side: "'Fortune Magazine/ Hot New Products' Good Morning America ABC-TV Network 12/08/93 7:00AM ET 0:45".
    - Fortune on TV, 1994 (Offsite-box 2915, Item 2)
      1 videocassette (VHS): On labels on case and cassette: "Fortune on TV 1994".
    - Fortune on TV, 1994 (Offsite-box 2915, Item 3)
      1 videocassette (VHS): On labels on case and cassette: "Fortune on TV 1994"
    - Fortune on TV, 1994 (Offsite-box 2915, Item 4)
    - Fortune on TV, 1994 (Offsite-box 2915, Item 5)
    - Fortune on TV, 1994 (Offsite-box 2915, Item 6)
    - Fortune on TV, 1994 (Offsite-box 2915, Item 7)
    - Fortune on TV, 1994 (Offsite-box 2915, Item 8)
      1 videocassette (VHS): On labels on case: "Fortune on TV 1994 PAL-European Only"
    - Marshall Loeb: Jim Hayes Retirement Skit: Fortune Week, 1994 (Offsite-box 2915, Item 9)
      1 videocassette (VHS): On label on case front: "Jim Hayes Retirement Marshall Loeb". On label on case side: "Marshall Loeb Jim Hayes Retirement Fortune Week Skit 1994".
    - Geoff Colvin: Fortune Business Report, 1994, January 24-27 (Offsite-box 2915, Item 10)
      1 videocassette (VHS): On label on cassette front: "Fortune Business Report Geoff Colvin Jan 24-27 GC". On label on cassette side: "Fortune Business Report Jan 24-27".
    - Geoff: Colvin: Fortune Business Report, undated (Offsite-box 2915, Folder 1)
      Previously enclosed with Geoff Colvin: Fortune Business Report, Box 2915 Item 10.
    - Tricia Welsh: Two Way Interview: NY1 News, 1994 January 26 (Offsite-box 2915, Item 11)
      1 videocassette (VHS): On cassette label: "NY1 Two Way Interview 1/26/94 Tricia Welsh". On label on case side: "NY1 News 1/26/94 Tricia Welsh".
    - Jim Hayes: You Can't Take That Away From Me, 1994 February 25 (Offsite-box 2915, Item 12)
      1 videocassette (VHS): On labels on case and cassette front: "Jim Hayes "You Can't Take That Away From Me" 2/25/94". On label on cassette side: "'You Can't Take That Away From Me'".
    - John Curran: Dow Drops 63 Pts.: CNN, 1994 March 29 (Offsite-box 2915, Item 13)
      1 videocassette (VHS): On label: "-Dow Drops 63 Pts.- CNN-John Curran-3-29-94".
    - John Curran: Dow Plunges 63 Pts.: CNN, 1994 March 29 (Offsite-box 2915, Item 15)
      1 videocassette (VHS): On label on case front: "CNN 3-29-94 John Curran Dow Plunges 63 Pts". On label on case side: "John Curran-CNN-3/29/94 Dow Plunges 63 Points".
    - Marshall Loeb on Business in South Africa: The Ten O'Clock News: WNYW-TV (Fox) New York, 1994 April 26 (Offsite-box 2915, Item 16)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (58 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Marshall Loeb on Business in South Africa' The Ten O'Clock News WNYW-TV (Fox) New York April 26, 1994 10:00-11:00 PM 0:58". On label on case side: "'Marshall Loeb on Business in South Africa' The Ten O'Clock News WNYW-TV (Fox) New York 4/26/94 10:00 PM 0:58".
    - Swaps and Derivatives, Fortune Magazine: CBS Evening News: CBS-TV, 1994 May 25 (Offsite-box 2915, Item 17)
      1 videocassette (U-matic)(2 min., 35 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Swaps and Derivatives, Fortune Magazine' CBS Evening News CBS-TV Network May 25, 1994 6:30-7:00 PM ET 2:35". On label on case side: "'Swaps and Derivatives, F.M.' CBS Evening News CBS-TV Network May 25, 1994 6:30-7:00 PM 2:35".
    - Fortune Magazine on Michael Carpenter, 1994 August 17 (Offsite-box 2916, Item 1)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (1 min., 5 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Fortune Magazine on Michael Carpenter' Today's Business C N B C August 17, 1994 6:00-7:00 AM ET 0:37 Business Morning Cable News Network August 17, 1994 6:30-7:00 AM ET 0:28". On label on case side: "'Fortune Magazine on Michel Carpenter' Cable Coverage August 17, 1994 (2 Segment-Schedule on Cover".
    - Lee Smith, Fortune Magazine: It's Your Business: WJLA-TV (ABC) Washington, 1994 August 28 (Offsite-box 2916, Item 2)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (17 min., 51 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Lee Smith, Fortune Magazine' It's Your Business WJLA-TV (ABC) Washington August 28, 1994 7:30 AM 17:51". On label on case side: "It's Your Business -- Lee Smith WJLA-TV (ABC) Washington 8/28/94 17:51 7:30 AM".
    - Geoff Colvin: Fortune Business Report, 1994 August 29 - September 2 (Offsite-box 2916, Item 3)
      1 videocassette (VHS): On labels on case front and cassette: "Fortune Business Report Talet: Geoff Colvin Dates: 8/29/94 - 9/2/94". Includes a sticker on front of case: "GC". On label on side of case: "Fortune Business Report Geoff Colvin 8/29/94-9/2/94".
    - Susan Kuhn: Romance in the Workplace, Fortune Magazine: A-T In Depth: AT Cable, 1994 September 15 (Offsite-box 2916, Item 4)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (8 min., 40 sec.): On labels on case: "'Romance in the Workplace, Fortune Magazine' A-T In Depth AT Cable September 15, 1994 6:00-8:00 PM ET 8:40 Susan Kuhn Int.". On cassette label: "'Romance in the Workplace, Fortune Magazine' A-T In Depth AT Cable September 15, 1994 6:00-8:00 PM ET 8:40".
    - Susan Kuhn: Romance in the Office: All Talk Network, 1994 September 15 (Offsite-box 2916, Item 5)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): On label: "Romance in the Office Susan Kuhn on All Talk Net. 9/15/94".
    - Shawn Tully: Healthcare Package: CNN, 1994 September 28 (Offsite-box 2916, Item 6)
      1 videocassette (VHS): On label on case front: "Shawn Tully on CNN Healthcare Package 9/28". On label on case side: "Shawn Tully on CNN Healthcare Package 9/28-94".
    - Geoff Colvin: Extra: WNBC, 1994 October 12 (Offsite-box 2916, Item 7)
      1 videocassette (VHS): On label: "10-12-94 Extra WNBC Geoff Colvin Discusses Katzenberg, Geffen, Spielberg Movie Deal".
    - Geoff Colvin: Extra, 1994 October 12 (Offsite-box 2916, Item 8)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (10 min., 24 sec.): On label on case front: "Katzenberg 10:24". On label in case side: "Katzenberg Extra 10-12-94 G. Colvin Discusses Katzenberg, Geffen, Spielber 10:24". On cassette label: "Katzenberg "Extra" 10:24".
    - Walter Kiechel: Asian Wall Street Journal Interview, 1994 October 25 (Offsite-box 2916, Item 9)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On label: "October 25, 1994 -- Best Cities in the World for Business-- W. Kiechel-Asian WSJ Report interv.".
    - Walter Kiechel/Fortune Magazine: CNN, 1994 October 25 (Offsite-box 2916, Item 10)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (3 min.): 3/4 in. On label on case front: "Walter Kiechel/Fortune Magazine CNN TV (Cable) October 25, 1994 6:25PM 3:00". On label on case side: "Walter Kiechel October 25, 1994 94 Best Cities". On cassette label: "Walter Kiechel October 25, 1994".
    - Walter Kiechel/Fortune Magazine: CNN, undated (Offsite-box 2916, Folder 1)
      Previously enclosed with Walter Kiechel/Fortune Magazine: CNN, Box 2916 Item 10.
    - FCC-PCS Auction, 1994 December 2 (Offsite-box 2916, Item 11)
      1 videocassette (VHS) (4 min., 15 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "FCC-PCS Auction TRT: 4:14 Date: 12/2/94 Prod. Hashimoto Edit. Satriale". Sticker on case front: "GC". On label on case side: "Fortune Hashimoto Satriale 12/2/94".
    - Walter Kiechel: Inside Business: CNN, 1994 December 25 (Offsite-box 2916, Item 12)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On label on case front: "Walter Kiechel on CNN Dec. 25, 1994 Inside Business Outlook for 1995". On label on case side: "Walter Kiechel on CNN's "Inside Business" 12/25/94 Year-End Wrap-Up, Outlook for 1995".
    - Walter Kiechel: Inside Business: CNN, 1994 December 25 (Offsite-box 2917, Item 1)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (6 min., 10 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Walter Kiechel' Inside Business CNN Cable December 25, 1994 11:30-12:00 AM 6:10". On label on case side: "Walter Kiechel on CNN's "Inside Business" 12/25/94 Year-End Wrap-Up, Outlook for 1995".
    - Geoffrey Colvin, Fortune Magazine Most Admired Corporations: Good Morning America Sunday: ABC-TV, 1995 February 19 (Offsite-box 2917, Item 2)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (3 min., 45 sec.): On label on case front and cassette: "'Geoffrey Colvin, Fortune Magazine Most Admired Corporations' Good Morning America Sunday ABC-TV Network February 19, 1995 9:00-10:00 AM ET 3:45". Sticker on case front: "5". On label on case side: "'Geoffrey Colvin, Fortune Magazine Most Admired Corp.' Good Morning America Sunday ABC-TV Network 2/19/95 9:00 AM 3:45".
    - Carol Loomis-Fortune Magazine: A-T In Depth: AT Cable, 1995 February 27 (Offsite-box 2917, Item 3)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (13 min., 25 sec.): On label on case front and cassette: "Derivatives Carol Loonis-Fortune Magazine" A-T In Depth AT Cable February 27, 1995 6:00-8:00 PM ET 13:25". On label on case side: "AT In Depth -- Carol Loomis Discusses Derivatives 2/27/95".
    - Alex Taylor: Fortune Business Report, 1995 April (Offsite-box 2917, Item 4)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On labels on case front and cassette: "Alex Taylor Appearance on The Fortune Business Report". On label on case side: "Alex Taylor -- Fortune Business Report -- April 1995".
    - John Gutfreund: Inside Opinion: CNBC, 1995 April 20 (Offsite-box 2917, Item 5)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On label: "CNBC "Inside Opinion" 4/20/95--John Gutfreund".
    - John Gutfreund: Inside Opinion: CNBC, 1995 April 20 (Offsite-box 2917, Item 6)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On label on case front: "CNBC "Inside Opinion" John Gutfreund 4/20/95". On label on case side: "CNBC "Inside Opinion" 4/20/95 John Gutfreund". On cassette label: "John Goodfreund April 20, 1995".
    - Carol Loomis, Fortune Magazine, Fortune 500: The Moneywheel: CNBC, 1995 April 25 (Offsite-box 2917, Item 7)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (3 min., 52 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Carol Loomis, Fortune Magazine/Fortune 500' The Money Wheel C N B C April 25, 1995 1:00-2:00 PM ET 3:52". On label on cassette side: "'Carol Loomis, Fortune Magazine Fortune 500' The Money Wheel CNBC 4/25/95 1:00 PM ET 3:52".
    - Carol Loomis: The Fortune 500: Moneywheel: CNBC, 1995 April 25 (Offsite-box 2917, Item 8)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On label: "CNBC--Moneywheel--Carol Loomis 4/25/95 The Fortune 500".
    - Patty Sellers, Fortune Magazine: Sunday Today in New York: WNBC-TV (NBC) New York, 1995 May 7 (Offsite-box 2917, Item 9)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (4 min., 5 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Patty Sellers, Fortune Magazine' Sunday Today in New York WNBC-TV (NBC) New York May 7, 1995 7:00-8:00 AM 4:05" Sticker on case front: "4". On label on case side: "'Patty Sellers' Sunday Today in New York WNBC-TV (NBC) New York 05/07/95 7:00-8:00 AM 4:05".
    - Gerald Levine: Shareholders Meeting: Market Wrap: CNBC, 1995 May 18 (Offsite-box 2917, Item 10)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (2 min., 11 sec.): On label on case front and cassette: "'Gerald Levine/Shareholders Meeting' Market Wrap C N B C May 18, 1995 5:00-6:00 PM ET 2:11". On label on case side: "T/W Shareholders MTG. 5/18/95 CNBC 'Marketwrap'".
    - Gerald Levine and Ann Reilly Dowd, 1995 May 18 (Offsite-box 2917, Item 11)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (35 min., 7 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Gerald Levin/Shareholders Meeting' Market Wrap CNBC-TV Cable May 18, 1995 05:00-6:00 PM 02:11 "Ann Reilly Dowd, Fortune Magazine" Washington Journal CSPAN-1 Cable May 18, 1995 06:00-12:00 PM 32:56". On label on case side: "Ann Reilly Dowd -- CSPAN 5/18/95".
    - Fortune Magazine: Flat Tax: 12 News Today: WWBT-TV (NBC) Richmond, 1995 May 30 (Offsite-box 2917, Item 12)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (45 sec.): On label on case front and cassette: "'Fortune Magazine/Flat Tax' 12 News Today WWBT-TV (NBC) Richmond May 30, 1995 6:00-7:00 AM :45". On label on case side: "'Fortune Mag./Flat Tax' 12 News Today WWBT-TV (NBC) Richmond 5/30/95 6-7 AM :45".
    - Shawn Tully, Fortune Magazine: Today's Business: CNBC, 1995 June 6 (Offsite-box 2918, Item 1)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (3 min., 40 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Shawn Tully, Fortune Magazine' Today's Business C N B C June 6, 1995 6:00-7:00 AM ET 3:40". Sticker on case front: "3". On label on case side: "'Shawn Tully, Fortune Magazine' Today's Business CNBC 6/6/95 6:00 AM 3:40".
    - Shawn Tully, Fortune Magazine: First Business: USA-TV, 1995 June 7 (Offsite-box 2918, Item 2)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (6 min., 5 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Shawn Tully, Fortune Magazine' First Business USA-TV Cable June 7, 1995 6:00-6:30 AM ET 6:05". On label on case side: "'Shawn Tully, Fortune Mag.' First Business USA-TV Cable June 7, 1995 6:00-6:30AM ET 6:05".
    - Fortune Magazine/Are You Paid Enough?: Good Morning America: ABC-TV, 1995 June 7 (Offsite-box 2918, Item 3)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (53 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Fortune Magazine/Are You Paid Enough?' Good Morning America ABC-TV Network June 7, 1995 7:00-9:00 AM ET 0:53". On label on case side: "'Fortune Magazine/Are You Paid Enough' Good Morning America ABC-TV Network 6/7/95 7:00 AM ET 0:53".
    - Shawn Tully, Fortune Magazine: Good Day Wake-Up: WNYW-TV (Fox) New York, 1995 June 15 (Offsite-box 2918, Item 4)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (3 min., 51 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Shawn Tully, Fortune Magazine' Good Day Wake-Up WNYW-TV (Fox) New York June 12, 1995 5:30-6:00 AM 3:51". On label on case side: "'Shawn Tully, Fortune Magazine' Good Day Wake-Up WNYNW-TV (Fox) New York 6/12/95 5:30 AM 3:51".
    - Rik Kirkland, Fortune Magazine: The Money Wheel: CNBC, 1995 June 13 (Offsite-box 2918, Item 5)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (6 min., 9 sec.): On label on case front and cassette: "'Rik Kirkland, Fortune Magazine' The Money Wheel C N B C June 13, 1995 10:00-11:00 AM ET 6:09". Sticker on case front: "2". On label on case side: "'Rik Kirkland, Fortune Magazine' The Money Wheel CNBC 6/13/95 10:00 AM ET 6:09 Death of Hong Kong".
    - Rick Tetzeli: Today's Business: CNBC, 1995 June 21 (Offsite-box 2918, Item 6)
      1 videocassette (VHS) (2 min., 55 sec.): 1/2 in. On label: "CNBC's "Today's Business" 6/21/95 Rick Tetzeli Setting Up Your Own Home Office 2:55".
    - Rick Tetzeli, Fortune Magazine: Today's Business: CNBC, 1995 June 21 (Offsite-box 2918, Item 7)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (2 min., 55 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Rick Tetzeli, Fortune Magazine' Today's Business C N B C June 21, 1995 6:00-7:00 AM ET 2:55". Stick on case front: "1". On label on case side: "'Rick Tetzeli, Fortune Magazine' Today's Business CNBC 6/21/95 6:00 AM 2:55"
    - Lee Smith: Fortune Magazine Trade Talks: Wake Up America: America's Talking, 1995 Jun 29 (Offsite-box 2918, Item 8)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (3 min., 30 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Lee Smith, Fortune Magazine Trade Talks' Wake Up America America's Talking June 29, 1995 7:00-8:00 AM ET 3:30". On label on case side: "'Lee Smith, Fortune Magazine Trade Talks' Wake Up America America's Talking 6/29/95 7:00 AM ET 3:30".
    - Rick Tetzeli: Cool Companies: WABC-TV, 1995 June 30 (Offsite-box 2918, Item 9)
      1 videocassette (VHS) (2 min., 53 sec.): 1/2 in. On label: "Rick Tetzeli-WABC-TV Cool Companie 6/30/95 2:53".
    - Rick Tetzelli, Fortune Magazine: Coolest Companies: Eyewitness News: WABC-TV (ABC) New York, 1995 June 30 (Offsite-box 2919, Item 1)
      1 videocassette (U-Matic) (1 min., 53 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Rick Tetzelli, Fortune Magazine/Coolest Companies' Eyewitness News WABC-TV (ABC) New York June 30, 1995 11:00-11:30 PM 2:53". On label on case side: "'Rick Tetzelli/Coolest Co.' Eyewitness News WABC-TV (ABC) New York 6/30/95 11:00 PM 2:53".
    - Rob Norton: Fortune Business Report, 1995 July (Offsite-box 2919, Item 2)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): On labels on case front and cassette: "Rob Norton Appearance on the Fortune Business Report". On label on case side: "Rob Norton -- Fortune Business Report -- July 1995".
    - Rob Norton, Fortune Magazine: How are things Financially: Good Day Wake-Up: WNYW-TV (Fox) New York, 1995 July 5 (Offsite-box 2919, Item 3)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (2 min., 41 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Rob Norton, Fortune Magazine/How Are Things Financially' Good Day Wake-Up WNYW-TV (Fox) New York July 5, 1995 5:30-6:00 AM 2:41". On label on case side: "'Rob Norton/How Things Are Financially' Good Day Wake-Up WNYWY-TV (Fox) New York 7/5/95 5:30 AM 2:41".
    - Susan Kuhn: Places to Retire: CNBC, 1995 July 6 (Offsite-box 2919, Item 4)
      1 videocassette (VHS) (3 min., 28 sec.): 1/2 in. On label: "Susan Kuhn-CNBC 7/6/95 3:28 Places to Retire".
    - Susan Kuhn, Fortune Magazine: Retirement: Today's Business: CNBC, 1995 July 6 (Offsite-box 2919, Item 5)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (3 min., 28 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Susan Kuhn, Fortune Magazine/Retirement' Today's Business C N B C July 6, 2018 6:00-7:00 AM ET 3:28". On label on case side: "'Susan Kuhn, Fortune Magazine/Retirement' Today's Business C N B C 7/6/95 6:00 AM ET 3:28".
    - Shawn Tully: Are You Paid Enough: Smart Money With The Dolans, 1995 July 13 (Offsite-box 2868, Item 1)
      1 audiocassette: analog, 4 1/2 x 2 1/2 in. Label on Side 1: "Shawn Tully-7-13-95 Are You Paid Enough?". Label on Side 2: "Smart Money with The Dolans 7/13/95 1-2 pm". Includes envelope which is labeled: "Are You Paid Enough WOR "Smart Money Woth the Dolans" Shawn Tully 7-13-95".
    - Lee Smith, Fortune Magazine: Today's Business: CNBC-TV, 1995 July 19 (Offsite-box 2919, Item 6)